本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
老公  你能想到这天不
Can you believe it, bob?
小查莉也要有第一张床了
Charlie's first big-girl bed.
她不是小宝宝啦  不用睡摇篮
She's not a baby anymore.
查莉啊  你喜不喜欢你的新床啊
Charlie, do you like your new bed?
不喜欢
No.
哎呀呀  感觉就是昨天的事儿呢
Oh, it seems like just yesterday
我好像还在抱怨要让出这房间来
I was complaining about giving up this room.
哟  你又怀念你的老房间啦  宝贝
Aw, you miss your old room, honey?
你开啥玩笑呢
Are you kidding?
现在我的房跟兄弟们隔了足足两层楼
There's two floors between me and the boys now.
我才不想这间老屋子呢
This room is dead to me.
我说啊  现在查莉有了自己的小床了
Hey, now that charlie's got her own bed,
那我可以开睡衣派对了吧
I can have a sleepover, right?
啥啊  怎么说着查莉有了新床
Okay, how did charlie's new bed.
就冒出来你要开睡衣派对了
Turn into you getting a sleepover?
让我给你们合计合计吧
Let me walk you through it.
天呐  我最爱这小子要来给咱合计这啊那的
Oh, I love it when he walks us through stuff.
每次我向你们要求开睡衣派对
Every time I ask you guys for a sleepover,
你们都说不行  因为家里有个小宝宝
You tell me I can't because there's a baby in the house.
现在好啦  刚才老爸说她不再是小宝宝了
Well, dad just said she's not a baby anymore.
你看他给咱合计好了吧
And he walked us through it.
还全忽悠成我的错了
And it's my fault.
听着  要是我再不邀请大家来家里过夜
Look. If I don't have a sleepover soon,
其他的孩子们以后也不会邀请我去了
The other kids will stop inviting me to theirs.
只要请小孩们来呆一晚上
One night of kids at our house.
就能日后无数夜晚把盖比这小鬼弄出家门
And we get rid of gabe for a bunch of nights.
答应他吧  这交易太合算了
Take it. It's a good deal.
- 好吧  你可以请大家来过夜了  - 太好了
- Fine, you can have your sleepover. - Yes!
过来呀  小查莉  来看看你的新床
Come here, charlie. Let's look at your new bed.
你一定会喜欢的
You'll love it!
不要
No
你一定很开心的费了两小时才组装起那玩意儿吧
I bet you're glad you spent two hours putting that together, huh?
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late,and dad jokes
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订： 山鹰逢羽
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
■
后期： line  追忆似水年华
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记第一季第十九集
Good Luck Charlie S01E19 Sleepless in Denver.
若你相信那会成真
If you believe it's true
若我心念念系你身
And if my heart's in you
不管你将要做甚
No matter what you do
都不会是孤单一人
You'll never face it alone
当天空撒下雨点
And when the rain leaks through
我也会在雨幕中等
I'll be right there with you
不管你将要做甚
No matter what you do
都不会留下孤单的身影
You'll never face it
不  你永远不会独自成行
No, you'll never face it alone.
我唱的怎么样
How was that?
我的天啊  爱丽丝  你是不是又犯哮喘啦
Oh my gosh. Alice, are you having an asthma attack?
没有啊  这是给你的大喝彩呢
No, that was the crowd cheering for you.
你唱的太棒了  不过刚才我最后发的声音是哮喘
You were great. That thing at the end, that was asthma.
谢谢你称赞
Oh thanks.
这是我第一次在高中音乐剧的试唱表演啊
It's my first audition for a high school show,
所以我绝对是想要出色表现的
So I really want it to go well.
别担心  因为我要给每个试演的人钢琴伴奏
Oh, no worries. Since I'll be playing. The piano for everyone's audition,
我保证在你唱的时候
When you're singing I'll make sure.
导演会看到我这种表情
The director sees me do this...
然后等其他学生试演时
And when the other kids are auditioning,
我就做这个
I'll do this...
哇  爱丽丝  你还真会做鬼脸呀
Wow. Alice, you make a really good stink face.
我们家住在污水处理厂旁边的呀
We live next to a sewage-treatment plant.
好啊
Hey.
PJ你来啦
Hey, p.J.
手里拿的是什么
What you go there?
一大杯烟熏肉
A cupful of bacon.
老哥  你要是不早点开始健康饮食
Dude, if you don't start eating healthier,
你很快就要肥起来的
You're gonna get fat.
泰迪  哥想吃啥就吃啥
Teddy, I can eat whatever I want.
吃不胖啊  好了  你们这边要是事完了
Nothing happens. Now if you're through here,
让我打个盹吧
I'd like to take a nap.
你干嘛不到楼上自己房间睡呢
Why don't you just go upstairs to your room?
因为这是我的第四杯熏肉了
'cause this is my fourth cup of bacon.
貌似有点醉醺醺的
And I'm feeling a little woozy.
我是不是打扰到你啦
I'm not bothering you, am I?
是有点啦
A little.
我能和您商量一下我的睡衣派对的事吗
Can we talk about my sleepover for a second?
盖比  你打断了我做家务呢
Gabe, you're distracting me from my housework.
我们当然可以来商量你这过夜派对的事
Of course we can talk about your sleepover.
那好  我先问一下
Ok, first question.
那天你准备给我们做什么晚饭吃
What are you serving us for dinner?
嗯  我想好了  要做我拿手的肉饼
Well, I was thinking of making my famous meatloaf.
还有很不错的配菜沙拉哦
With a nice side salad.
那就定匹萨了
Pizza it is.
还有  我想请你帮我们去借恐怖电影的碟
Okay, now I'm gonna need you to rent us a scary movie.
不好吧  盖比  我不想让你们兴奋一整晚
I don't know, gabe. I don't want you boys to be up all night.
老妈  你刚所说的就是最完美的睡衣派对形式啊
Mom, you just described the perfect sleepover.
那么最后一件事项
Now the last thing is...
查莉在墙上涂鸦呢
Charlie's writing on the wall.
什么
What?
我是说  查莉她
Charlie...
正在墙上乱涂呢
She's writing on the wall.
我会画画儿
I can draw.
小查莉啊
Charlie.
PJ  吃早饭了
P.J., breakfast!
大家早上好
Morning, everybody.
我快饿死了
I'm starving.
你是不是又卡在那里啦
Are you stuck again?
老妈  得给门再抹些黄油
Mom, put some more butter on the door.
咱家没黄油了  都被你哥吃光了
We're out of butter. He ate it all.
我早说你会变肥仔的
I told you you were gonna get fat.
孩子们  快帮你们大哥系上保险背带
Kids, help your brother into his harness.
直升机来接他上学了
The helicopter's here to take him to school.
不要啊
No...
哎哟喂
Ooo!
哟  还有熏肉呢
Ooh, bacon.
比卢普斯老师  那个  你好哇
Hi, um, mr. Billups.
我是泰迪·邓肯  我嘛  有点想来报名
I'm teddy duncan. I'd, um, like to sign up.
就是参加"美女与野兽"剧目的试演会
To audition for "Beauty and the beast."
邓肯小姐  作为演剧者
Miss duncan, in the theater.
你必须表现出极大的自信
One must present oneself with confidence,
不能含含糊糊的说"好像"或是"嗯啊"的这种
Not with "Like" And "Um."
现在你重来说一次
Now reenter and say it again.
这一次你得表现出非常想的意愿
This time like you want it.
好吧
Okay.
您好  比卢普斯老师  我是泰迪·邓肯
Hello, mr. Billups. I'm teddy duncan.
让我加入你的音乐剧吧  拜托了
Put me in your show! Please.
好一点了  现在你唱一组和弦试试
Better. Now give me an arpeggio.
你让我就在这走廊上唱啊
Right here in the hallway?
快唱
Arpeggio.
还不错  那你舞跳的怎么样
Fair. How's your dancing?
您想不想再听我唱点啥呢
Would you like to hear me sing again?
泰迪  你要是多多努力的话
Teddy, with a lot of hard work,
还是有可能成为我的女主角的
You might have a shot at being my beauty...
真的吗
Really?
如果啦  我是说如果
...If... and I mean if...
你得表现出极大的激情给我看  让我哇塞叫出来
You can show me some passion. You've got to wow me.
目前我可是没有哇塞叫的打算哦
And so far I'm not being wowed.
那个  真是好抱歉
Well, I'm... I'm really sorry.
不行不行不行  给我重来
No no no no no. Give it back to me.
对着我的脸说
Get in my face.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry!
明天的试演会  你就得带着这腔调过来
Tomorrow at the audition, you've got to really bring it.
就当我帮也要帮过来
Consider it brung!
你是说绑过来吧
You mean "Brought."
别来纠我错儿
Don't correct me!
我就爱你这调调
I love it!
果汁真好喝
This juice is great.
太好喝了
Really really great.
我在家里时  他们不让我吃甜的
I'm not allowed to have sugar at home.
我倒是想问问原因了
I... huh... wonder why.
说得对  看来我们该让你换喝水吧
Yeah. Maybe we should switch you to water.
别啊
No!
多赞的过夜派对啊
What an awesome sleepover.
史上最强的
The best one ever.
赞德仔啊  你刚来了十分钟  安分点先
Xander honey, you've been here 10 minutes. Pace yourself.
这匹萨上面放了芝士乳酪的吗
Does this pizza have cheese on it?
因为我不能吃芝士乳酪的
'cause I can't eat cheese.
那给我吃吧
I'll eat it.
利安姆啊  你想不想吃花生酱三明治呢
Liam, would you like a peanut butter sandwich?
不用了  谢谢  我也对花生过敏
No thanks. I'm allergic.
那也给我吃吧
I'll eat it.
我们等下要看什么电影啊
What movie are we gonna watch later?
嗯  我想是这个
Well, I was thinking
"小猴摘香蕉"
"Monkeys go bananas."
这是一部欢乐有趣的卡通剧
It's a delightful and funny cartoon.
讲的就是猴子们去摘香蕉的故事
About monkeys who just go bananas.
那是给六岁小孩看的呀
That's for six-year-olds.
才不是呢  上面写的是适合四岁以上
No, it says "Four and up."
失陪
excuse me.
妈妈  我们稍许谈一下好吗
Mom, can I talk to you for a second?
当然可以
Sure, yeah.
来  到这边来
Come on. Okay. Let's go.
你还不如直接杀了我算了
You're killing me here!
我要你去借的那个电影"僵尸戮血大会"呢
Where's the movie I asked you to get, "Zombie blood party"?
我是借到了啦  不过我不确定可以给你们看
Well, I got it, but I'm just not sure.
盖比  那部看来太血腥暴力了
Gabe, it looks very violent.
就是要这个主题啊
That's kind of the point.
现在赶紧去宣传宣传吧
Now get over there and sell it!
快去快去
Come on. Let's go.
我们还有另一个选择就是
Our other choice is
"僵尸戮血大会"
"Zombie blood party"...
太棒了
Awesome!
这部是讲僵尸的
...Which is about zombies.
开一个血腥大会
Who just have a blood party.
好极了
Yeah!
牛逼
All right!
好了  孩子们  后院已经架好帐篷了
Okay, guys. We've got the tent set up in the backyard.
只要等你们吃完饭
So once we're done eating...
我看他们算是吃完了
I guess they're done eating.
那孩子可能还想看看点心单呢
He might want a dessert menu.
你在干什么
What you doing?
做锻炼
Working out.
以防日后我得坐直升机去上学
So I don't have to go to school in a helicopter.
一如既往的  我只能听懂一半你的话
As usual, I only understood half.
喂喂  儿子  等下等下
Hey, p.J. , wait wait wait.
咋啦
What?
你在举哑铃前得先做做伸展运动
You've got to stretch out before you pump the iron.
不然你想伤到自己吗
You want to hurt yourself?
不想啊
No.
那你过来这边
Hey, come here. Come here.
让我给你稍微示范一下
Let me show you a little something.
先来摸脚趾运动  好吧  跟着我做就行了
Do some toe-touches, all right? Just do what I do.
行啊
You do, okay.
我们开始吧
Here we go. Ready?
一  二
One and...
哎哟
Ow!
哎哟  哎哟  哎哟
Ow! Ow! Ow!
不是  不是  不是  不是
No! No! No! No!
不是不是  我觉得我扭到脚筋了
No no, I think I pulled a hamstring.
你们在干什么啊
What are you guys do...
哎呀喂  老爹的屁股  雷晕了我
Oh! Dad butt! Ow!
这也太酷了吧
Isn't this cool?
就是
Yeah.
咱们好好闹腾整晚吧
Let's stay up all night.
至少我肯定睡不着
I know I am.
真的呀
Yeah.
这地面好硬啊
This ground seems kind of hard.
利安姆  因为那是地
Liam, it's the ground.
大地本来就是硬的
That's how the ground always feels.
喂  把门拉起来  让谁也进不来
Hey, zip up the door so no one else can get in.
等下  我们还是能再要些吃的吧  对不
Wait. We're still gonna be able to get more food, right?
好了  现在确定了  查莉真的是不爱她那新床
Well, it's official. Charlie hates her new bed.
这孩子又犯啥幺蛾子了
Now what's going on with her?
在墙上乱画呢  根本不肯上床睡觉
Writing on walls. Won't sleep in her bed.
哎哟  老公  可不能小看这个娃
Well, bob, she's an overachiever.
她提早在1岁半就开始尝试2岁小恶魔行当了
She started her terrible twos at one and a half.
让我来哄她吧
Bring her over here.
哟  阿爸要来亲子乐哦
Aw, daddy wants quality time.
是呀  哎呀呀  另一边  另一边啦
Yeah. Oh! Oh! Other side. Other side.
好啦  来抱抱
There we go. There we go.
真是对不起
Really sorry.
没事  这样就好多了  没事啦
It's okay. It's better. It's all better now.
你还真的是把老骨头给伤到啦
You really hurt yourself, huh?
是哦
Yeah, well,
所以我才需要去锻炼嘛
That's what I get for trying to exercise.
天哟  还好我总算是过了那周期了
Boy, I'm glad that chapter's closed.
哇  那是咋回事
Whoa, what's that?
呀  你有没有关了自动洒水器
Oh, did you turn off the automatic sprinklers?
咱家还有装自动洒水器的么
We have automatic sprinklers?
简直就像掉进了洗衣机里出不来
It was like being trapped in a washing machine.
我还以为要给淹死了
I thought I was gonna drown.
这整晚都被毁啦
The whole night is ruined.
放松点  我们还能补救的啦
Relax. We can fix this.
怎么补救啊  我们是要睡在帐篷里
How? We were gonna sleep in the tent,
还要在帐篷里看电影
Watch a movie in the tent,
还要在帐篷里做些我不能告诉你的事
Do stuff I couldn't tell you about in the tent.
得了  盖比  你们不如就上楼去
Hey, gabe, look. Why don't you just go upstairs,
在自己房间玩过夜派对  至于PJ么
Have a sleepover in your room and then p. J....
PJ他反正可以在地下室的沙发上睡觉
P.J. Can sleep on the couch in the basement.
对呀对呀  我还可以再给你们订个匹萨来
Yeah yeah, and I'll order another pizza.
这次记得告诉他们多放些腊肠
Tell them to put more pepperoni on this time.
之前我都看见上面的乳酪了
I could still see cheese.
注：腊肠匹萨上肉片应该覆盖满整个表面
呃  小利安姆啊  你有什么事吗
Uh, liam honey, is there a problem?
人家害怕上楼
I'm afraid of upstairs.
啥意思
Excuse me?
我家是住平房的
We live in a one-story house.
我这辈子都没上过楼  也不要从今天开始上
I've never been upstairs and I'm not gonna start now.
真有意思的新型恐惧症
Interesting new phobia.
好吧  过夜派对改到地下室进行吧
Okay, sleepover's in the basement.
你不会害怕下楼去吧  怕么
You're not afraid of downstairs, are you?
才不  我又没疯
No, I'm not crazy.
我说亲爱的  要是让他们去楼下
Hey, honey, if he goes downstairs,
那不就是说他最后就
Doesn't he eventually have to...
别别别
No no no no.
老公啊  一次解决一个好伐
One battle at a time, honey.
等等  要自信  要激情
Okay, wait. Confidence. Passion.
这次比刚才还要糟啊
That one stunk worse than the first.
睡袋大战啊
sleeping bag fight!
你们吵什么啊
What are you doing?
睡衣派对改到地下室来了
Sleepover's been moved to the basement!
不是吧  不要啊
No! No!
你们在这里这么吵  我在那边睡不着的啊
Well, I can't sleep in there if you're making noise out here.
哎呀  说得好
Oh. Good point.
抓住她
Get her!
这电影真好笑
This movie's hilarious.
这些小猴子真是疯颠颠的
These monkeys are going absolutely crazy.
果然是四岁以上啊
Yup, four and up.
他们还真没写错年龄层呢
They got that right.
喂  老爸  我怎么没觉得起效啊
Hey, dad, I don't see any difference yet.
你做了几次啦
Well, how long have you been doing it?
已经两次啦
Twice.
妈妈  你是不是叫那些小男生睡到楼下去的
Mom, did you tell the boys they could sleep downstairs?
哎呀宝贝  他们没别的地方可以睡嘛
Well, honey, they don't have anywhere else to go.
那好  我是不会去PJ的房里睡的
Okay, well, I'm not going into p.J.'s room.
你们又都在一楼这  那叫我去哪边睡觉啊
And you guys are down here, so where am I supposed to sleep?
我家的傻瓜父母
Stupid parents.
我听见了哦
Heard that.
晕  这傻瓜宝宝监控器
Oh. Stupid baby monitor.
别进去那里啊
Don't go in there.
别进去啊
Don't go in there!
别去
Don't go...
哎呀  老兄  他真的不该进去的
Oh, man, he shouldn't have gone in there.
记住  没人可以逃脱
Remember, no one is safe.
僵尸无处不在
The zombies are everywhere!
无处不在
Everywhere!
这电影不错吧
That was a good movie, huh?
我看我是再也睡不着了
I don't think I'm ever gonna sleep again.
你干嘛要借这么恐怖的电影来看啊
Why'd you have to get such a scary movie?
我想回家
I want to go home.
我也是
Me too.
得啦  哥几个  你们不会是害怕一堆僵尸吧
Come on, guys. You're not afraid of a bunch of zombies, are you?
好吧  我去楼上跟我爸妈说
Fine. I'll go upstairs and tell my parents.
楼上吗
Upstairs?
晕  我之前怎么就没想到这茬
Oh, man, I really didn't think this through.
嘿  小哥儿  情况如何啊
Hey, buddy. How's it going?
糟透了  大家都想回家去
Terrible. Everyone wants to go home.
为啥啊
Why?
都怪你借来的那个电影
Because that movie you rented us.
那部完全不适合我们看
Was completely inappropriate.
我的第一次睡衣派对完全是场悲剧
My first sleepovers a total disaster.
好啦宝贝  放松点好吗
Oh honey. Relax, okay?
我去跟你的小伙伴们聊聊
I'll go have a little talk with them.
一切都会好的
Everything's gonna be fine.
好了  小子们给我听着
Okay, everybody listen up!
僵尸不是真的  现在全部上床睡觉去
Zombies aren't real! Now go to bed!
大家晚安
Good night, everybody.
啊喔  这玩意儿果然有效果
Ah. Wow, this is really paying off.
看来真的是
It sure is.
儿子啊  帮我个忙
Hey, p.J., do me a favor...
搭把手拉我起来吧
Would you give me a hand up?
行啊
Yeah.
喂  那可是我最喜欢的胳膊呀
Hey, that's my favorite arm.
哟喂  我现在壮的过头了
Oh now. I'm too strong now.
儿子  儿子
P.J. P.J.
PJ啊
哟  喔
Ow! Oh!
哎哟  我的脚啊
Oh, my foot!
对不起  爸爸  你没事吗
I... I'm sorry, dad. Are you okay?
哎哟
Ow!
啊  我跟你说吧
Ah. You know what?
我还是上床去睡吧
I should just go to bed.
在我睡觉前  我还得去看看楼下的男孩子们
Before I go to bed, I've got to go check on the boys.
哎哟我的腿哟
Oh, my thigh.
哎哟我的脚哟
Oh, my foot.
哎哟我的腿  哎哟我的脚
Oh, my thigh. Oh, my foot.
腿啊  脚啊
My thigh. My foot. Ah!
哥们  哥们  快醒醒
Guys. Guys, wake up.
怎么了
What is it?
你们听
Listen!
越来越近了
It's getting closer!
是僵尸啊
Zombie!
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
攻击啊
Attack!
对准脑袋打  瞄准脑袋啊
Aim for the brain! Aim for the brain!
对  快打啊
Yeah! Get him!
哇哇哇  哎哟
Whoa whoa whoa! Oh!
喂
Hey!
等等  兄弟们  停手  停手
Wait, guys! Stop! Stop!
那是我爸啊
That's my dad!
你爸是僵尸吗
Your dad's a zombie?
我才不是僵尸
I'm not a zombie.
证据呢
Prove it.
哎哟
Ow!
他能感到疼痛  看来我们安全了
He feels pain. We're okay.
老爸  你来干什么啊
Dad, what are you doing?
我只不过来看看你们而已啊
I'm just checking on you guys.
像僵尸一样走过来吗
Like a zombie?
现在他们又要想回家去了  真是多谢你
Now they're gonna. Wanna go home again. Thanks a lot.
我可不想回家呀  这太有劲了
I don't wanna go home. That was awesome.
有劲吗
It was?
是呀
Yeah.
你都被吓坏了
You were so scared.
我可没被吓坏
I wasn't scared.
你才被吓坏了
You were scared.
我才是最被吓不轻的那个
Not as scared as me.
我们再玩一次吧  邓肯叔
Let's do it again, mr. Duncan.
别来了  我得睡觉了
No no no. I've got to go to bed.
老爸老爸  来玩嘛
Dad dad, come on.
请尽量满足孩子们吧
Give the kids what they want.
好吧
All right.
很好  开始吧
Yeah, let's go.
好吧
Okay.
这可真好玩
This is so cool.
你们死定了
Must kill.
老爸老爸  僵尸不会说话的
Dad dad dad, zombies don't speak.
对不起喔
Sorry. Uh...
早上好啊  查莉
Good morning, charlie.
看看你呀
Look at you.
你是不是个小画家呀
Are you an artist? Huh?
你是在哪儿画了画儿嘛
Did you paint a picture somewhere?
还行  墙壁看来是保住了
Oh. Well, the walls look okay.
哎呀我的天  我试演要迟到了
Oh my gosh! I'm late for my audition!
我糟
Uh-oh.
谢谢
Thank you.
爱丽丝  大家都唱完了吗
Alice, is that everyone?
哦还没有  泰迪·邓肯还没来呢
Oh no, teddy duncan isn't here yet.
别别  对不起  我来了  我来了
No no no. Sorry. I'm coming. I'm here.
用这个
there.
泰迪  你怎么啦
Teddy, what happened to you?
睡过头了
I overslept.
行了
Okay.
大家好
Hi.
我要唱的曲子是
I'm going to be singing
"永不让你孤单"  请弹吧
"You'll never face it alone." Hit it.
若你相信那会成真
If you believe it's true
若我心念念系你身
And if my heart's in you
不管你将要做甚
No matter what you do
都将不会孤单一人
You'll never face it alone
停停  你在搞啥啊
Stop stop. What was that?
在试演啊
I was auditioning.
为啥角色呢  美女还是野兽哇
For what, beauty or the beast?
当然是美女了  我干嘛要去演野兽啊
Well, beauty of course. Why would I be auditioning for the beast?
我是说  那是  那是因为我看上去像野兽啊
I mean, that's something... that's because I look like a beast.
你为何要在脸上乱涂呢
Why do you have scribbles all over your face?
你是不是想表达美貌只是皮囊
Are you trying to say that beauty is only skin deep.
真正美的是人的内心
And what's inside is what's truly important?
其实吧
Well, actually...
因为若你是这个意思
Because if you are,
我喜欢这表现
I love it.
那就确实是我要表达的东西
Then that's exactly what I was going for.
哇
Whoa.
嘿嘿  查莉  你现在高兴了吧
Hey, charlie, are you happy now?
换回小摇篮床啦
No more big-girl bed.
对哟  因为你妈坚持说我们再也不需要围栏床
Yes, and since mommy insisted we'd never need the crib again,
结果老爸我只好去买了个新的(旧的被他们处理了)
Daddy gets to go buy a new one.
老爸大概也得睡回自己的老床了(让他睡沙发)
Daddy might be sleeping in his own bed too.
好消息啊  伙计们
Great news, you guys!
今天我收到三个过夜派对邀请
I got invited to three sleepovers today!
老爸  其中有2个连你也请了
And, dad, you got invited to two of them.
什么啊  我可不想去什么睡衣派对
What? I don't want to go to any sleepover.
老爸  这是一揽子交易  你必须去
Dad dad, we're a package deal. You're going.
就是那样  你留着到晚上再用吧
That's it. Now save that for tonight.
好吧  小查莉
Well, charlie,
你又睡回自己的宝宝床啦
You're going back to your crib.
我也得到自己的席位了
And I'm going places too...
我拿到学校音乐剧的主角了耶
I got the lead in the school musical.
我会成为史上最棒的野兽
I'm gonna be the best beast they've ever had.
现在才是真正的大新闻
Here's some really big news.
我要健康饮食了
I'm eating healthy now,
因为我决定了  就喜欢自己现在的样子
Because I decided I like mysetf just the way I am.
行了  她才不感兴趣
Yeah, she's not interested. Ok.
还有一件事  你要是再敢在我脸上乱画试试
One more thing: If you ever draw on my face again...
祝你好运了  查莉
...Good luck, charlie.
那是什么声音啊
What's that noise?
是僵尸来了吗
Is that a zombie?
爸  你那套过时了啦
Dad, that's getting old!
什么过时了
What's getting old?
如果你在这儿  那谁在外面
If... if you're there, then who's...
哇呀
Whoa!
这些疯颠颠的猴子们哟
Oh those crazy monkeys!